3. 2.01-To verify the details displayed on the Sign In Welcome Screen
2.02-To verify the details displayed on the "Sign In Registration" Screens
2.03 To verify the Username/Password validation  on the "Sign In Registration" Screen
2.04 To verify the validation for the Progress bar present on the "Registration" and "2FA" Screen
2.05 Verify the "I need help in entering details" link
2.06-Verify the sign in step 2 of 4 screen details & validations [2FA Screen]
2.0 6 a) -Verify the navigation back to 2FA Screen from Sign 1 of 4 screen
2.07-To verify the Sign In process when Mobile number is linked to account 2FA
2.09 - To verify the "Sign in step 3 of 4" screen details
2.10 - To verify the "Sign in step 3 of 4" screen validations
2.11 - To verify the "Sign in step 4 of 4" screen details
2.12 - To verify the "Sign in step 4 of 4" screen validations
2.13 - To verify the Incorrect PIN validations on the  "Sign in step 4 of 4" screen
2.16-To verify whether the user is able to skip the Fingerprint/Face ID authentication during Registration - Maybe later
2.22 More - Verify the Sign out process for the PIN, Fingerprint and Face ID logins
2.24-To verify the "Sign In" Screen for  the new user login using 6 - digit PIN
2.27 - Verify the screen, when user close and invoke the OneCS application without making the choice between the following two options [Enable biometrics & Maybe later]
1. startApplication("bs://70ba423167486281f805009f4439403483e6bc4d", true)
1. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/logo"), 0)
5. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Create a secure"), 0)
9. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Sign in"), 0)
13. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Sign in Button"), "Sign in")
17. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Dont have an account"), "Don't have an account?")
21. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Create one on our website"), "Create one on our website")
25. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Create one on our website"), 0)
29. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.Button - Accept All"), 0)
33. continuebutton = getText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/weburl"), 0)
37. Assert.assertEquals(continuebutton, "charles-stanley.co.uk/services/save")
41. pressBack()
45. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/logo"), 0)
49. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Sign in Button"), 0)
53. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Sign in step 1 of 4"), "Sign in step 1 of 4")
57. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/X_Button"), 0)
61. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Username  password"), "Username & password")
65. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Please enter your username and password associated with your Charles Stanley account"), "Please enter your username and password associated with your Charles Stanley account.")
69. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "")
73. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "")
77. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/eyebuttoninsignin"), 0)
81. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "bob", 0)
85. clearText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), 0)
89. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "Pass123$", 0)
93. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "••••••••")
97. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/closebutton"), 0)
101. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/logo"), 0)
105. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Sign in Button"), 0)
109. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "bob", 0)
113. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "pass123$", 0)
117. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "bob")
121. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "••••••••")
125. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Continue"), 0)
129. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Details incorrect"), 0)
133. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Details incorrect"), "Details incorrect")
137. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Please check the details youve entered are correct"), "Please check the details you've entered are correct.")
141. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Edit details"), "Edit details")