1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/OneCSMobile-SignIn_Registration.feature")
1. startApplication(bsApp, true)
1. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/logo"), 0)
5. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Create a secure"), 0)
9. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Sign in"), 0)
13. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Sign in Button"), "Sign in")
17. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Dont have an account"), "Don't have an account?")
21. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Create one on our website"), "Create one on our website")
25. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Create one on our website"), 0)
29. Bool = verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.Button - Accept All"), 10)
33. if (Bool == true)
1. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.Button - Accept All"), 0)
37. continuebutton = getText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/weburl"), 0)
41. Assert.assertEquals(continuebutton, "charles-stanley.co.uk/services/save")
45. pressBack()
49. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/logo"), 0)
53. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Sign in Button"), 0)
57. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Sign in step 1 of 4"), "Sign in step 1 of 4")
61. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/X_Button"), 0)
65. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Username  password"), "Username & password")
69. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Please enter your username and password associated with your Charles Stanley account"), "Please enter your username and password associated with your Charles Stanley account.")
73. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "")
77. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "")
81. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/eyebuttoninsignin"), 0)
85. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "bob", 0)
89. clearText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), 0)
93. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "Pass123$", 0)
97. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "••••••••")
101. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/closebutton"), 0)
105. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/logo"), 0)
109. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Sign in Button"), 0)
113. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "bob", 0)
117. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "pass123$", 0)
121. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "bob")
125. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "••••••••")
129. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Continue"), 0)
133. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Details incorrect"), 0)
137. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Details incorrect"), "Details incorrect")
141. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Please check the details youve entered are correct"), "Please check the details you've entered are correct.")
145. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Edit details"), "Edit details")
149. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Edit details"), 0)