3. E2E Regression for IMS Portal Five Point Health Check
1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("http://kdx03:Servehugematch93!@clientsupport.sit.charles-stanley.co.uk/app/")
9. maximizeWindow()
1. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/button_Create new"))
5. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Select Service IMS OneStep - Five-po_f58547"), "2", true)
9. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Dashboard/button_Create new"))
13. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/span_Business getter code_anchor"))
17. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/li_MRL - Aaron Murphy"))
21. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/span_Client Details"))
25. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Select titleMrMsMrsMissDrOther"), "1: Mr", true)
29. setText(findTestObject("Page_Dashboard/input_First names_client1firstnames"), "AutoTest")
33. setText(findTestObject("Page_Dashboard/input_Last name_client1lastname"), "AutoLast")
37. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Date of birth_client1dob"), "10/10/1993")
41. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Gender_gender1"))
45. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectSingleMarriedSeparatedD_f061ed"), "Single", true)
49. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectSingleMarriedSeparatedD_f061ed"), "Single", true)
53. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectSingleMarriedSeparatedD_f061ed"), "Single", true)
57. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/a_Or enter address manually"))
61. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Address line 1_addressLine1"), "fsdfdsgfd")
65. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Address line 2_addressLine2"), "gfadsgdfgfdg")
69. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Address line 3_addressLine3"), "gfdgfdgdf")
73. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_TownCity_town"), "gdfgfdgdaf")
77. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_County_county"), "gdfgfdg")
81. setText(findTestObject("Page_Dashboard/input_Postcode_postcode"), "NW87QJ")
85. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_United KingdomAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican_c00340"), "Argentina", true)
89. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Email address_client1email"), "auotestkat@gmail.com")
93. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Home telephone_client1hometelephone"), "123454567")
97. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Mobile telephone_client1mobiletelephone"), "85462323")
101. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Work telephone_client1worktelephone"), "234356567")
105. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Communication and Marketing Preferenc_8fce92"))
109. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Communication and Marketing Preferenc_b744b6"))
113. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/span_Risk Questions"))
117. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Disagree_riskQuestionsClient120Answer75"))
121. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Strongly disagree_riskQuestionsClient_869c13"))
125. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Neither agree nor disagree_riskQuesti_b96afd"))
129. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Strongly disagree_riskQuestionsClient_f3727a"))
133. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Agree_riskQuestionsClient124Answer97"))
137. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Disagree_riskQuestionsClient125Answer100"))
141. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Agree_riskQuestionsClient126Answer107"))
145. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Agree_riskQuestionsClient127Answer112"))
149. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Disagree_riskQuestionsClient128Answer115"))
153. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Disagree_riskQuestionsClient129Answer120"))
157. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Agree_riskQuestionsClient130Answer127"))
161. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_When considering investing, I would d_f9f055"))
165. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_I would regret deciding not to take a_6fba81"))
169. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_The term I most closely associate wit_3dfdd1"))
173. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_I take risks at every opportunity_ris_ad1f78"))
177. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/textarea_Any further notes about the questi_bff76a"), "Hi verifiying katalon POC")
181. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/span_Additional Client Details"))
185. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Select NationalityBritishAfghaniAlba_eb0c08"), "British", true)
189. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Select NationalityBritishAfghaniAlba_eb0c08"), "British", true)
193. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectUnited KingdomAlbaniaAl_f3487d"), "United Kingdom", true)
197. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectUnited KingdomAlbaniaAl_f3487d"), "United Kingdom", true)
201. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Based on this description, do you thi_bdfd1b"))
205. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/textarea_Details_client1-politically-exposed-text"), "gfdhfjgjkgkghkghjgh")
209. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Passport_verificationIdType1"))
213. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Driving licence number_client1-drivin_e255d6"), "fsdfgdaghfdh234")
217. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Expiry date_client1-expiry-date"), "10/12/2036")
221. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectFull-Time EmployedPart-_fbbedb"), "null", true)
225. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectFull-Time EmployedPart-_fbbedb"), "null", true)
229. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectFull-Time EmployedPart-_fbbedb"), "Full-Time Employed", true)
233. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectFull-Time EmployedPart-_fbbedb"), "Full-Time Employed", true)
237. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Expected retirement age_client1-emplo_dac0ea"), "45")
241. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_OccupationJob title_client1-employed-_f9375d"), "Fishing")
245. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Name of employer Company name_client1_eaba97"), "Katalon")
249. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Nature of business employment_client1_ffa724"), "Private")
253. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectUnited KingdomAlbaniaAl_f3487d_1"), "null", true)
257. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectUnited KingdomAlbaniaAl_f3487d_1"), "null", true)
261. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectUnited KingdomAlbaniaAl_f3487d_1"), "United Kingdom", true)
265. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_Please selectUnited KingdomAlbaniaAl_f3487d_1"), "United Kingdom", true)
269. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_Under 2 years"))
273. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Under 2 years_hasQualifications1"))
277. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/textarea_Education details_client1-qualific_f35bc7"), "fsdfdgdah")
281. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Yes_hasFinancialDependents1"))
285. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/span_Financial Details"))
289. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty"), "234")
293. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_Add"))
297. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1"), "234")
301. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2"), "456")
305. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3"), "123")
309. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4"), "678")
313. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5"), "456")
317. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6"), "100")
321. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7"), "222")
325. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8"), "111")
329. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_Withdraw"))
333. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9"), "234")
337. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Are you a member of a Defined Benefit_824ca8"))
341. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10"), "222")
345. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11"), "111")
349. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12"), "234")
353. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13"), "444")
357. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14"), "321")
361. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15"), "456")
365. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16"), "234")
369. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid n_6110fe"), "256")
373. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Anticipated payoff date_undefined"), "12/12/1980")
377. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16_17"), "111")
381. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid n_6110fe_1"), "345")
385. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Anticipated payoff date_undefined_1"), "11/11/1964")
389. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16_17_18"), "343")
393. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16_17_18_19"), "345")
397. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-valid ng-touched ng-dirty"), "111")
401. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16_17_18_19_20"), "333")
405. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16_17_18_19_20_21"), "222")
409. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16_17_18_19_20_21_22"), "456")
413. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16_17_18_19_20_21_22_23"), "123")
417. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16_17_18_19_20_21_22_23_24"), "456")
421. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16_17_18_19_20_21_22_23_24_25"), "888")
425. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16_17_18_19_20_21_22_23_24_25_26"), "222")
429. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16_17_18_19_20_21_22_23_24_25_26_27"), "222")
433. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-valid ng-dirty_1_2_3_4_5_6_7_8_9_10_11_12_13_14_15_16_17_18_19_20_21_22_23_24_25_26_27_28"), "111")
437. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Yes_willNetAnnualIncomeChangeInNext12Months1"))
441. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Yes_isOtherFinancialInformationAvailable1"))
445. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/span_Five Point Health Check"))
449. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/button_Save application"))
453. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/span_How would you describe your health"), "How would you describe your health?")
457. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/span_Please select an option"), "Please select an option")
461. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_How much money would you like to set _e99e76"), "How much money would you like to set aside for emergencies? (enough money to pay 3-6 months worth of expenses)?")
465. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_In the event you cant work due to inj_2e7536"), "In the event you can’t work due to injury or illness, would you continue to receive income from your employer or an insurance policy that you have?")
469. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_In the event of your death, is there _bc5d02"), "In the event of your death, is there any provision for your family/dependents from your employer or an insurance policy that you have?")
473. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_In the event of your death, will ther_b3c401"), "In the event of your death, will there be any outstanding liabilities like critical regular expenses, mortgage or loan repayments?")
477. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_Do you have an up to date will"), "Do you have an up to date will?")
481. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_Have you set-up a Power of Attorney"), "Have you set-up a Power of Attorney?")
485. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_How much is outstanding"), "How much is outstanding?")
489. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_How much are the monthly repayments"), "How much are the monthly repayments?")
493. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_Please select the applicable type"), "Please select the applicable type:")
497. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_What is the interest rate"), "What is the interest rate?")
501. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_What year will the mortgage be repaid"), "What year will the mortgage be repaid?")
505. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_Please list any significant future sp_19701b"), "Please list any significant future spending goals that you are planning? (Please consider any near, medium and longer term goals).")
509. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_Please provide any other information _e49286"), "Please provide any other information you feel may be relevant to enable us to provide guidance and/or advice that is suitable for your needs.")
513. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_ok_healthCondition1"))
517. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/textarea_Please provide further details bel_579585"), "HI this is Katalon")
521. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control dark-control ng-untouch_3b60e3"), "222")
525. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Please select an option_continueToRec_a41e6b"))
529. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/textarea_Please provide further details bel_ff7668"), "Hi this is Katalaon")
533. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Yes_provisionForFamilyInCaseOfDeath"))
537. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_No_liabilitiesInCaseOfDeath"))
541. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Yes_haveUptodateWill"))
545. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_Health and Welfare Lasting Power of Attorney"), "Health and Welfare Lasting Power of Attorney")
549. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_Power and Financial Affairs Lasting P_f970d7"), "Power and Financial Affairs Lasting Power of Attorney")
553. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_Enduring Power of Attorney (if set-up_b88b61"), "Enduring Power of Attorney (if set-up before 2007)")
557. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/label_Other type of Power of Attorney (plea_03612b"), "Other type of Power of Attorney (please provide further details below)")
561. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Or Please tick all applicable_five-po_b5c783"))
565. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/textarea_Other type of Power of Attorney (p_79955f"), "Hi this is Katalon")
569. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control dark-control ng-untouch_636786"), "222")
573. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control dark-control ng-untouch_636786_1"), "123")
577. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_What is the interest rate_form-contro_764aad"), "444")
581. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_What year will the mortgage be repaid_749b19"), "2020")
585. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/a_Add spending plan"), 0)
589. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/a_Add spending plan"), "Add spending plan")
593. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/a_Add spending plan"))
597. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input_Target date (Year)_form-control dark-_5177ce"), "Shipping")
601. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control dark-control ng-untouch_3b60e3_1"), "2000")
605. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/input__form-control ng-untouched ng-pristin_178ccb"), "2013")
609. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/span_Remove"), 0)
613. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/textarea_Additional Information_five-point-_69f99e"), "Hi This is Katalon")
617. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/button_Save application"))
621. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/span_Summary"))
625. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/button_Publish settings"))
629. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off"), "1: 1", true)
633. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off"), "1: 1", true)
637. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1"), "1: 1", true)
641. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1"), "1: 1", true)
645. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1_2"), "1: 1", true)
649. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1_2"), "1: 1", true)
653. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1_2_3"), "1: 1", true)
657. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1_2_3"), "1: 1", true)
661. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1_2_3"), "1: 1", true)
665. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1_2_3_4"), "1: 1", true)
669. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1_2_3_4"), "1: 1", true)
673. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1_2_3_4"), "1: 1", true)
677. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1_2_3_4_5"), "1: 1", true)
681. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1_2_3_4_5"), "1: 1", true)
685. selectOptionByValue(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/select_UnpublishedPublishSigned off_1_2_3_4_5"), "1: 1", true)
689. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/button_Save changes"))
693. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/IMS Objects/Page_Dashboard/button_Publish settings"), 0)
697. closeBrowser()