1. startApplication(bsApp, true)
5. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Sign in Button"), 0)
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Sign in step 1 of 4"), "Sign in step 1 of 4")
13. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/X_Button"), 0)
17. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Username  password"), "Username & password")
21. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Please enter your username and password associated with your Charles Stanley account"), "Please enter your username and password associated with your Charles Stanley account.")
25. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "")
33. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/eyebuttoninsignin"), 0)
37. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/SignIn/android.widget.TextView - Ive forgotten my details"), 0)
41. getDriver().closeApp()
45. getDriver().quit()