1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/Android_Registration.feature")
1. startApplication(bsApp, true)
1. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/logo"), 0)
5. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Create a secure"), 0)
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Sign in Button"), "Sign in")
13. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Dont have an account"), "Don't have an account?")
17. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Create one on our website"), "Create one on our website")
21. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Create one on our website"), 0)
25. continuebutton = getText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/weburl"), 0)
29. Assert.assertEquals(continuebutton, "charles-stanley.co.uk/services/save")
33. pressBack()
37. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/logo"), 0)
41. getDriver().closeApp()
45. getDriver().quit()
1. startApplication(bsApp, true)
1. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Sign in Button"), 0)
5. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Sign in step 1 of 4"), "Sign in step 1 of 4")
9. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/X_Button"), 0)
13. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Username  password"), "Username & password")
17. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Please enter your username and password associated with your Charles Stanley account"), "Please enter your username and password associated with your Charles Stanley account.")
21. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "")
25. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "")
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/eyebuttoninsignin"), 0)
33. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/SignIn/android.widget.TextView - Ive forgotten my details"), 0)
37. getDriver().closeApp()
41. getDriver().quit()
1. startApplication(bsApp, true)
1. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Sign in Button"), 0)
5. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "onecsapps", 0)
9. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "Cupholder1", 0)
13. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Continue_Button"), 0)
17. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/SignIn/android.widget.TextView - Sign in step 2 of 4"), "Sign in step 2 of 4")
21. pressBack()
25. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "onecsapps")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "••••••••••")
33. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Continue_Button"), 0)
37. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/SignIn/android.widget.TextView - Verify your account"), "Verify your account")
41. getDriver().closeApp()
45. getDriver().quit()