1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/Android_More.feature")
1. startApplication(bsApp, true)
1. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Sign in Button"), 0)
5. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Sign in step 1 of 4"), "Sign in step 1 of 4")
9. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/X_Button"), 0)
13. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Username  password"), "Username & password")
17. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/android.widget.TextView - Please enter your username and password associated with your Charles Stanley account"), "Please enter your username and password associated with your Charles Stanley account.")
21. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Usernamefiled"), "")
25. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/Passwordfiled"), "")
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android Objects/eyebuttoninsignin"), 0)
33. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Object Repository/SignIn/android.widget.TextView - Ive forgotten my details"), 0)
37. getDriver().closeApp()
41. getDriver().quit()